

Dante Terranova

Contact

Address Moreno, Buenos Aires

Phone +54 113-191-8140

Email dante_jterranova463@hot mail.com

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/ in/dante-juanterranova-2383361a4/

Personal website

https:// binaryjuan.github.io/ portfolio/

Github

https://github.com/BinaryJuan

Summary

My name is Dante Terranova, i am a 21 year old who is passionate for the IT field, more specifically in the website development area as a **full-stack developer**. My main knowledge encompasses both Frontend and Backend, although i am an 'always learning' individual. My native language is Spanish, but i have an advanced level of English which makes me able to communicate efficiently.

Education

Bartolomé Mitre Day School | 03/2013 - 12/2018

- Secondary school (native spanish)
- Bilingual economics bachelor and organization management
- International exams: PET, FCE, IGCSE Cambridge (Maths, English, Literature, Sociology, Spanish literature, Environmental management, computer science)
- English level: C1 Advanced
- · General skills: Figma, Microsoft Office, Photoshop

National University of Luján | 03/2019 - Present

- University
- Degree in Information Systems (IT)

Coderhouse | 09/2021 - 10/2022

- Full-stack developer career
- Degrees in HTML/CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, Backend (<u>see degrees</u>)
- Main skills: HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Git, Python, Delphi, ReactJS, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase, Webpack, basic Typescript

Domestika | 06/2022 - 06/2022

Web design with Figma (Pablo Stanley)

Work experience

Web programmer for Diesel Avenida | 08/2021 - 04/2022

- Static web programming using HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Maintenance

Freelance front-end developer | 04/2022 - 06/2022

· Project for Quinta Silveria, a wedding event facility